maire by your side
I always thought irony was a mistake the
best mistake one could ever make
Agis cowboy the years haven't changed
too much have they Jesse they certainly
haven't changed my feelings about
working with you
dr. Zhao I'm interested in your
colleagues research into the long-term
effects of cryogenic freezing oh well
yes I am sure maybe
describing your work as unethical would
be a kindness but the true question is
whether or not you can deny my
discoveries
no I didn't think so
well I must never worry about my safety
when the brave agents of helix are with
us don't be so sure about that
your condition seems relatively stable
no one's accused me of that in a long
time
grace to overwatch if I had known what
Reyes had been planning I would never
have allowed it it seems to me that it
was convenient for you not to look too
closely into Gabriel's business
how are you feeling Lacroix I don't feel
that's the point isn't it
Winston you are never frustrated at the
restrictions overwatch placed on your
research of course but sometimes a
measure of caution is needed in a
scientist
over watch had good reason to shut down
your research I shouldn't be surprised
at such a narrow opinion coming from a
jumped-up ape
I must know how your technology
functions existence is mysterious isn't
it
harridan
our guardian angel